Vonnegut, Bernard; Papers ua902.068
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1938-1997; Undated; 10; 7 cubic ft.
  - General Electric - Research Laboratory, 1946-1951; 1954; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Grenet, 1947-1994 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Griffiths, 1948; 1972-1979; 1983; 1989 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 35-36)
  - Gaston Gronet, 1945; 1947; 1959-1960 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Gunn, Ross, 1966 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - H, 1965-1975; 1977-1989; 1991; 1994 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Heffernan, Warm Cloud Electrification, 1957 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Helgafell Volcano, Heimacy, 1973 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Henderson, Thomas J, 1968-1997 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - High Voltage Generators, 1956; 1967-1971 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Hobbs, Peter, 1983; 1985 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Holeworth, R.H, 1974; 1981; 1983-1987; 1989 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Hollister, Walter M., 1985 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Holloman, Herb, 1969; 1984-1985 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Holzer, Rob T.E., 1955; 1962-1963 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Howard, John A., 1969; 1971-1976 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Howell, Wallace, 1941-1942; 1965-1967; 1969; 1986 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Huges, James, 1955; 1961; 1974-1977; 1981-1986; 1988 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 15-16)
  - Huges, James C - 59667, 1957-1958; 1961-1971 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 17-18)
  - Huges, James, Appreciation, 1988 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Huges, James, Dinner, 18, May, 1988 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - J. Hughes Plaque, 1984; 1988 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Jeremy HYLKA "Alert Illinois" Tornado Research Team, 1991-1994 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - I, 1962-1969; 1971; 1973-1975; 1980-1983 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - ICAE, 1994-1996 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Iceland, 1964 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 25-26)
  - Iceland, 1965 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Imianitov. I.M, 1965; 1985; 1987 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Initiation of Lightning Discharges on Demand, Winder, Ron, 1964-1965 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Israelson "Fallout", 1990 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - J, 1963-1970; 1972; 1975-1976; 1986-1987; 1989-1990 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1963-1965 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - K, 1963-1994 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 33-34)
  - Kuttner, Joachim Mct. Rundschau, 1950 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - L, 1963-1973; 1975; 1977-1989; 1991; 1993-1994 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Lane-Smith, Dereck, 1968-1974; 1977-1978 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Langmuir, Irving, 1993; 1996 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Langmuir, Irving "Hurricane", 1945; 1955 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Langmuir I. Studies of the effects produced by dry ice seeding of stratus clouds, Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Lansford: Mosaic Article About Global Circuit, 1982-1983 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - John Latham, 1964-1965; 1967-1969; 1982-1983; Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - John Latham, 1974; 1976-1977; 1982-1983; 1985-1986; 1988-1991 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - LEIPSIG, 1996 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Leob, Leonard B, 1963; 1965; 1970-1971 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Lescarboura, Julio, 1967 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Alan Lightman, When do anomalies Begin? Science 7 Feb 91, 1992 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Lightning, 1994 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Lomonosov, 1987; 1992 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Lukomski, Hieronim, 1964-1965 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - M, 1963-1994 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 17-18)
  - MacCready, Paul B. (Dr), 1964; 1970; 1977; 1985 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Malon, D.J., 1962-1963; 1965 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Martell, E.A, 1958; 1970-1972; 1983-1984 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Mason Day, Fri May 11 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Mason, S.G., 1965-1970; 1976; 1979-1980; 1985-1987 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Mazur, Vladislav, 1982; 1984; 1988 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - McC, 1962-1970; 1972-1973; 1977; 1989; 1992 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Martell, E.A, 1958; 1970-1972; 1983-1984 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - McMahon, Howard and Tom, 1963; 1966-1970; 1983-1984; 1986-1988 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Media, 1975; 1978-1983 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Mekcher & Zahn (MIT), 1969-1970; 1973; 1989 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Michnowski, Stanislaw, 1966-1996 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Michnowski, Stanislaw, Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Moondust, 1964-1965 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Museums - Center for Exploration, Children's Museum, Indianapolis, 1987-1988 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - N, 1962-1969; 1981; 1984 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - NASA, 1962-1966 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - National Geographic, 1990; 1993 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - National Science Foundation - [RESTRICTED], 1962-1989 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Newton's Apple "Tornadoes", Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Nifuku, Masaharu, 1973-1977 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - O, 1964-1966; 1970-1975; 1977; 1980; 1984 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Office of Naval Research - [RESTRICTED], 1966-1971 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Office of Naval Research, 1966-1971; 1973; 1982 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - P, 1961-1994 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 2-3)
  - ATM Electr. Pageoph, 1982-1983; 1987-1988 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Passarelli-Camera Flights, 1976 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - re: Passarelli experiments, 1972-1973; 1980 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Passarelli, R.E., Jr., 1972-1974; 1982-1983; 1987 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Perkin- Elmer, 1982 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence - Notes of Appreciation, 1947; 1949-1950 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Petterssen, Sverre, 1963; 1967-1968; 1996 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Popular Mechanics, 1963 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Pounder, Colin, 1975-1979; 1986 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - D.E. Proctor Letter: Malam + CTR, 1970-1971; 1974; 1991 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Q, 1963-1964; 1981 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Quaker Oats Co., 1974 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - R, 1958-1996 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 16-17)
  - Radioactivity, 1964-1966 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Ralston Purina, 1975; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Reinhardt, Nick, 1968-1974; 1976-1977 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Research Corporation, 1972-1973 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Review Ohanian Chapter Atmospheric Electric Norton Co. Drake Mcfeely, 1983-1985 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Review Krider and Roble "The Earths Electrical Environment", 1985 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - R.R. Rogers (McGill) A Short Course in Cloud Physics, 1980-1981 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Royal Meteorological Society, 1964-1966; 1968; 1972 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Russian Weather MOD Article, 1967 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Ryan, Bob, 1968-1996 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - S, 1961-1996 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 28-31)
  - Saffer Charles, 1995 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Sanders Frederick, 1978; 1985 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Saturday Review, 1965-1968; 1970 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - V.J. Schaefer, 1954-1993 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 35-36)
  - VJS Library, 1982 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Vincent Schaefer and Snow Makings by Katherine B. Blodgett, 1947-1948 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Schwarz, Joe, 1992; 1994 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Science, 1964-1992 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Science Fortnightly, Inc., 1965 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Science History, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - U.S. Senate Committee on Commerce 3/8/66, 1966 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Senate Com. Inferior & Insular Affairs 3/23/66, 1966 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Paul Silberg, 1957; 1963; 1965; 1976-1978; 1981-1982 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Paul Silberg, Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Silverman, Sam (DR.), 1974; 1977-1978; 1984-1985 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Joanne Simpson, 1963-1995 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Sprites etc., 1993-1996 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Standler, Ronald, 1970-1973; 1976 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Stanford, John L., 1971-1972; 1975-1976 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - State University of New York at Albany, 1965-1969; 1971-1981; 1985; 1991 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4-5)
  - State University of New York at Albany - "The Atmosphere" Art Museum Show, 1993 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - State University of New York at Albany, Mary Fiess Update, 1987 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Static Electricity Sensor For Helicopters, Army Fort Eustes, VA, 1979 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Stith, Jeffrey L, 1985 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Stockmayer, Walter, 1949 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Stockmayer Walter, 1973; 1975; 1982-1983; 1987 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Stone, Robert G., 1970-1971 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Strange, John P, 1964; 1966; 1968 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Sugar Explosions, 1965 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Surtsey, 1965 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - The Swiss Watch by John Leimert, Undated (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - T, 1962-1994 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 17-18)
  - Hannes Tammet, USSR, 1964; 1975-1977; 1984-1985; 1992 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Bill Taylor ELF, 1986 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Taylor, Sir Geoffrey, 1965-1967; 1969 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Thor Guard, 1975 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - A.J. Thrope Weather, 1981; 1988; 1991 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Trefethen, L., 1985 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Turnball, David, Undated (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Twitchell, Paul, 1989 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - U, 1962-1967; 1970-1972 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - UCAR Cups Research Project, 1980 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - UFO Articles, 1966 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - USA Today, 1995 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - V, 1958-1988 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - W, 1959; 1961-1980; 1982-1985; 1991; 1993-1997 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 32-34)
  - Weather Modification Association, 1994 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - WMO Technical Note, 1974-1975 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Observations Hurricane Alicia R.T Walter, 1983 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Rob't Watts, Tulane U. Theory of Prester Tornadoes, 1971-1975 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Weather Bureau, 1964-1966 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Wegener, 1992 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Weickmann, Helmut, 1965; 1967-1968 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Weide Robert B., 1994 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Weyer, J.R, 1966; 1968; 1974 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - John Willett, 1972-1974; 1976; 1980-1983; 1991 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 44-45)
  - Earle Williams, 1975-1976; 1979-1994 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 46-47)
  - E Wms 2/5 Ms, 1986 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - William Dale Williams, 1974 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Wise, George (GE), 1984 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Wood, C.A. "Unusual lightning", 1951 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Whyaduck Production, 1996 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Wyckoff, Pete, 1965-1969; 1971-1972 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 53)
- Audio/Video, 1955-1996; Undated; 11; 2.8 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically
  Dr. Vonnegut's audio/visual series consists of materials related to his research and presentations as well as the work done by some of his colleagues, especially Duncan Blanchard and Vincent Schaefer. The formats included in this series are VHS, cassette, reel to reel, " open reel, 8 mm film, super 8 film, and 16 mm film. Visual materials come in both color and black and white formats. Items have been titled based on Dr. Vonnegut's own identification system. Any audio or video which Dr. Vonnegut did not name are listed as Untitled.
  - 41D Video 1) Lightning (Sit Camera) Time In GMT 2) Payload Assist Module Burn, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 1)
  - Aerology-Thunderstorms Pt. 1 Formation and Structure of Thunderstorms (MN-7409-A), Undated (Film 1)
  - Aerology-Thunderstorms Pt. 2 Flight Techniques with Respect to Thunderstorms (MN-7409-B), Undated (Film 2)
  - Atmospheric Electricity, Undated (Film 3)
  - Bentley - all Things Considered - D. Blanchard, Undated (Cassette 1)
  - Bernie's Discussion of Optical Signal Detection 0-300 Counts, NOSL Hardware Test at Norman, Oklahoma (300-381), Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 2)
  - Bernie Talk, Undated (Film 4)
  - Bob Ryan, Waterspout Tornado, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 3)
  - BV AMS Nuclei Film, Undated (Film 5)
  - The Coalescence of Liquid Drops, Undated (Film 6)
  - Copy of Hatlidi Jousson Electrostatic Vortex, 1991; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 4)
  - Conquest Pt. II - WX Data (2), Undated (Film 7)
  - Cyclone, Undated (Film 8)
  - Dr. John Howard 3 3/4 1/ds 1/4 TRK, Undated (Reel 1)
  - Dr. John Howard 3 3/41ds 1/4TRK, Undated (Reel 2)
  - Dr. John String - New Kirk Flight, Undated (Film 9)
  - Dr. Kevin's Bubble, Undated (Film 10)
  - E. Wind VJS etc. DCB Tornadoes Gidven, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 5)
  - Electrostatic Vortex Tonsson and BV, 1991; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 6)
  - EDC #212 Vonnegut's Tornado FTG. Orig EKTA, Undated (Film 11)
  - Fermi Lab Tornado Seminar Tape 1, 1991; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 7)
  - Fermi Tornado Seminar (Excerpts) Tape 2, 1991; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 8)
  - Gas Jet Turbulence Schliereh, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 9)
  - GBI Pt. 2, 1959 (Film 12)
  - General Electric Highlights for Langmuir Project, 1996; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 10)
  - Goddard Space Flight Center " CBS Conquest 1958 Simpson Cloud Studies", 1991; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 11)
  - ICAE VII Session 1 (0-3875) - Session 2 (3880-5362), Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 12)
  - ICAE VII Session 3 (0000-3114) Session 4 (3210-5080), Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 13)
  - ICAE VII Session 5 (0-2895) Session 6 (up to 5104) Session 7 (til end), Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 14)
  - ICAE VII Session 7-II; Session 8, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 15)
  - ICAE VII Session 10-2 / Conference Summary, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 16)
  - ICAE VII Banquet Speeches, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 17)
  - Jets Whittle and Von Ghain, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 18)
  - John Howard, 1974; genreform: 1/2" Open Reel (Video-tape 19)
  - Lightning and Time-Lapse Video Recordings of Clouds over Langmuir Laboratory and N.M. Tech - C.B. Moore, 1991; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 20)
  - Lightning-Nova, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 21)
  - Red Sprites and Blue Jets Luminous Discharges above T-Storms University Alaska, 1994; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 22)
  - Mason Day, 1979; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 23)
  - McConnel AFB Tornado, 1991; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 24)
  - Mt. Redoubt Eruptions, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 25)
  - Night and Day Opt. Survey of Lightning (NOSL), Undated (Film 13)
  - NOSL Equipment - Norman, Okla - "Lightning During Severe Thunder Storms", 1980 (Film 14)
  - NOSL - Norman, Okla, 1980 (Film 15)
  - NOSL/STS-4 Mag, 301, 305, 307 (Master), Undated (Film 16)
  - Nova's Story of Penicillin 0-1480, 1986; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 26)
  - - ? Oklahoma ? Midwest City Cloud-TL D-142 T.L. Clouds, 1956 (Film 17)
  - Pesetsky Discovery CBM CTR Wilson, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 27)
  - Plainfield Tornado Dick Moore Before Zola, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 28)
  - Simulated LTG Test 1078" DA Hole for Strobe Source, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 29)
  - Skylab-3 Day-249 TV-71 Liquid Motion H-02443, Undated (Film 18)
  - STS-4 NOSL Master, Undated (Film 19)
  - STS-6 NOSL, 1983; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 30)
  - "Surface Chemistry" by Dr. Irving Langmuir, Nobel Prize Laureate in Chemistry, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 31)
  - STS-30, 1989; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 32)
  - Surtsey - with Whirlwinds, Undated (Film 20)
  - Time Lapse Video Recordings of Clouds over the Magdalena Mountains of New Mexico from the Lemitar NM Camera; Langmuir Lab, NM Tech Socorro, NM, 1991; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 33)
  - Temps d'un Eclaire - St. Privat Allier, Undated (Film 21)
  - T.L. High Alt. Baloon, 1955 (Film 22)
  - The Tornado: Approaching the Unapproachable, Undated (Film 23)
  - Tornadoes, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 34)
  - Tornados Misc., Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 35)
  - Untitled, Undated; genreform: 1/2" Open Reel (Video-tape 36)
  - Untitled, Undated (Film 24)
  - Untitled, Undated (Film 25)
  - Upward Lightning - JR Winkler, U Minn July 1989 - Science July 1990, 1989-1990; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 37)
  - Video Observations of Uppser Atmosphere Optical Flashes Recorded from the NASA DC-8 Over the Midwest, 1993; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 38)
  - Vince Schaefer "A" Roll Dub, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 39)
  - Vonnegut Copy of Master, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 40)
  - Vonnegut "A" Roll Dub, Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 41)
  - Vonnegut-Moore 1957 DOC Orig. Koda. DL. (1957 Mt. Washington N.M. Field Trip Original) (Film 26)
  - "The Weather Channel", Undated; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 42)
  - When Lightning Strikes with Tom Skilling, 1992; genreform: VHS (Video-tape 43)